garena.co.id 2012-11-10

# Garena Indonesia - Connecting world gamers

Welcome to the garena.com website run by Garena Interactive Holding Limited. ("Garena," "we," "us," or "our"). Garena is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of our garena.com website (the "Site") (we refer to the Site and the services we provide as described in our Site collectively as the "Garena Features"). As such, we have established and implemented this privacy statement to inform visitors to the Site and users of the Garena Features how we use and protect the information we collect. If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, please see the section entitled "Questions? Contact Us" at the end of this privacy statement. 

WHAT INFORMATION DOES GARENA COLLECT? 

Garena does not collect personally identifiable information unless our visitors voluntarily provide it to us. We do, however, collect certain types of information and ask for personal information in certain circumstances, such as when you set up an account. The following sections describe what type of information we collect, when we collect it and how we use it. 

SETTING UP AN ACCOUNT 

In order to use certain functionality of the Garena Features, you will have to create a user account which requires you to submit certain personal information. When you register and create an account, we require you to provide us your name and email address as well as a user name that you select. We also ask for certain information about yourself such as your age, birthdate, gender and interests. Upon activating an account, you will select a user name and password. Your user name and password will be used so you can securely access and maintain your account. 

VIEWING WEB PAGES 

As with most web sites, your computer sends information that gets logged by a web server when you browse our Site. This typically includes your computer's IP address, operating system, browser name/version, the referring web page, requested page, date/time, and sometimes a "cookie" (which can be disabled using your browser preferences) to help the site remember your last visit. If you are logged in, this information is associated with your personal account. The information is also included in anonymous statistics to allow us to understand how visitors use our site. 

COOKIES 

We may from time to time implement "cookies" or other features to allow us or third parties to collect or share information that will help us improve our Site and the Garena Features we offer, or help us offer new services and features. A cookie is a small amount of data, that often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to a user's browser from a Web server and stored on a user's computer hard drive. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personal information about you. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of our Site or the Garena Features. 

VIEWING AND DOWNLOADING CONTENT AND ADVERTISING 

As with browsing web pages, when you watch content and advertising or download games and other software on our Site or through the Garena Features, most of the same information is sent to us (including, IP Address, operating system, etc.); but, instead of page views, your computer sends us information on the content, advertisement or game viewed or installed by the Garena Features and the website and time. Additionally, the Garena Features allow us to collect information regarding the games you have installed and uninstalled on your computer and what time you start and stop playing a game. 

COMMUNITY & SUPPORT 

We provide customer service support through email and feedback forms. In order to provide customer support, we will ask for your email address. Aside from this information, we do not ask for any personal information to provide customer support. We only use information received from customer support requests, including email addresses, for customer support services and we do not transfer or share this information with any third parties. 

You can also post questions and answer other user questions in our community forums. Our forum and messaging services allow you to participate in our gaming community; to do so, we maintain information, such as your user ID, contact list, and status messages, including what game you are currently playing (if you explicitly choose to enable this option). In addition, these and similar services in the future may require us to maintain your User ID and password. 

SURVEYS 

From time-to-time, we request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as your email address), and demographic information (such as interests or age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Garena Features and will not be transferred to third parties. 

HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE US? 

As stated above, we use your personal information such as your name, user ID and email address to maintain your user account. We also will use your email address to contact you when we provide customer support and to inform you when another user has sent you a private message or posted a comment for you on the website. 

In addition, from time to time, we may also use your email address to send you information on updates to the Garena Features, and unless you choose not to be included, to alert you to offerings from other companies that we are affiliated with. We will not ever sell your email address or send you offerings from companies that we are not affiliated with. 

We may also provide aggregated information about our visitors to outside parties from time to time. We may use the information we collect to tailor your experience through the Garena Features by displaying content according to your interests and preferences, providing a faster method for you to access your account and submit information to us and allowing us to contact you, if necessary. 

HOW DOES GARENA PROTECT CUSTOMER INFORMATION? 

We implement a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems. User personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems. We continue to store your personal information for so long as it is necessary to provide you our service and currently do not anticipate destroying old personal information. In most cases, we will at a minimum keep one archival copy of your information to allow us to comply with laws or respond to legal processes. 

DOES GARENA DISCLOSE THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS FROM ITS VISITORS TO OUTSIDE PARTIES? 

We will never sell or rent your email address or any of your personal information. Unless we get your explicit approval in advance, we will only share your personal information as we believe is necessary to: 

keep you updated, respond to, confirm or fulfill your requests, and notify you of service issues and unusual account actions; enforce our Terms of Service or the Garena End User License Agreement; protect personal safety and the rights, property or safety of others; comply with laws or respond to legal processes; allow for a change of ownership of Garena and associated transfer of all personal information to the new owner of Garena, in which case your information still remains protected under this Privacy Policy; allow third party suppliers, vendors, contractors and other parties to provide products and services to us or to you, or to otherwise act on our behalf (this may include, without limitation, us authorizing such third parties to email our users regarding updates, surveys and other inquiries regarding their experience with the Garena client and service); allow for advertising and other audits, and surveys to, among other things, validate the size and composition of the gaming audience, and understand its experience with the Garena client and service. This may require, among other things, disclosing your gaming history and/or disclosing records showing which games were viewed by which IP addresses. We will also share statistical and demographic information about our users and their use of the Garena Features with suppliers of advertisements and programming. This would not include anything that could be used to identify you or to discover individual information about you. 

Additionally, you may elect to export your user activity feeds as RSS feeds which may be subscribed to by other users, which may include information regarding your game play, installation of games, connections with other users and other information about your account activity which is published as a feed on the Site. 

INFORMATION ON CHILDREN 

The Garena Features are not intended for children under the age of 10. We do not knowingly collect or maintain any personal information or non-personally-identifiable information from anyone under the age of 10 nor is any part of our Site or other Garena Features directed to children under the age of 10. We will close any accounts used exclusively by such children and will remove and/or delete any personal information we believe was submitted by any child under the age of 10. 

HOW DO YOU CHANGE THE INFORMATION WE HAVE FOR YOU? 

To update, modify or delete the information that we have on file for your account, simply go to the "My Account" section of the Site, log in, then modify your details and settings as necessary. Please note that we require at least a valid email address from you in order to maintain your account. 

INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THIRD PARTIES 

Our Site uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We, and third parties, may from time to time make software applications and game downloads available for your use on or through the Garena Features. These applications may separately access, and allow a third party to view, your identifiable information, such as your name, your user ID, your computer's IP Address or other information such as what game you are playing during any given session, and any cookies that you may previously have installed or that were installed for you by a third party software application or website. Additionally, these applications may ask you to provide additional information directly to third parties. Third party products or services provided through these applications are not owned or controlled by Garena. You are encouraged to read the terms and other policies published by such third parties on their websites or otherwise. In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, we may choose various third party web sites to link to, and frame within, the Site. We may also participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to our visitors. However, even if the third party is affiliated with us, we have no control over these linked sites, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us. Data collected by our co-brand partners or third party web sites (even if offered on or through our site) may not be received by us. As such, we have no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such web sites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of the Garena Features and the links placed upon each of them and therefore request any feedback on not only the Garena Features, but for sites each links to as well (including if a specific link does not work). EU SAFE HARBOR COMPLIANCE 

We adhere to the European Safe Harbor principles as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personally identifiable information collected from citizens of the European Union. 

For more information, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor. 

NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES 

By visiting the Site or using the Garena Features, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set forth in this privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes within this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

QUESTIONS? CONTACT US 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or your dealings with the Garena Features, please do not hesitate to contact: support@garena.com 

TERMS AND CONDITIONS 

Please also read the Terms of Service establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the Site and the Garena Features.
